[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following characters was not seated on the couch or chairs in the reject section at the Omega House rush party in the movie Animal House?", "correct_answer": "Franklin", "incorrect_answers": ["Jugdish", "Mohammed", "Sydney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a belief,  women should wear diamonds on this finger.", "correct_answer": "The middle finger of the left hand", "incorrect_answers": ["The thumb of the right hand", "The index finger of the left hand", "The middle finger of the right hand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these popular musicians was not born in Spain?", "correct_answer": "Shakira", "incorrect_answers": ["Paco de Lucia", "Alejandro Sanz", "Enrique Iglesias"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Fight Club, Tyler Durden is seen 3 times before the narrator glimpses him on the moving walkway at the airport.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope Princess Leia tells Grand Moff Tarkin that the rebel base is where?", "correct_answer": "Dantoine", "incorrect_answers": ["Alderaan", "Tatooine", "Endor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This architectural term, which refers to a free-standing bell-tower, comes from Italian and means a high bell tower.", "correct_answer": "Campanile", "incorrect_answers": ["Cellula", "Mensole", "Triforium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of Bahrain?", "correct_answer": "Manama", "incorrect_answers": ["Niamey", "Bahrain City", "Muscat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Robert De Niros character show fits of rage towards his brother Joey in the movie Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "He thought he was having an affair with his wife.", "incorrect_answers": ["He wanted sole possession of his parents estate.", "He crashed his car and didnt tell him.", "He spent all his money gambling."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Gene Hackmans character, Coach Norman Dale, suspended from coaching NCAA basketball?", "correct_answer": "Assaulting one of his players", "incorrect_answers": ["Gambling on the sport", "Recruiting violations", "Kicking a referee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the informal association of people who can trace their ancestry to the original Virginian colonists from England?", "correct_answer": "First Families of Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["First children of Virginia", "First Settlers of Virginia", "Founders of Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Clarks family in the National Lampoons Vacation series?", "correct_answer": "Griswold", "incorrect_answers": ["Robinson", "Murry", "Chase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the taste of the popular Indonesian soup called Sayur Asem?", "correct_answer": "Sweet and sour", "incorrect_answers": ["Very salty", "Bittersweet", "Hot and spicy"]}]